Ajay has happened, he has happened
that
[Music]
Hello, today in this video I will talk about
Confusion 2300, the help that you get in between, Bhupar
's Pressure Plan and Star Comprehensive
Health Tonic,
friends, I am your life insurance consultant Kajal, I will keep you updated about turmeric and life insurance through this channel and will give you advice on every problem related to this point, friends, in this video we are
watching this channel, if you
share this video with at least 10 people and comment, then the
best comment will be from my side
because I will
give it and those who
want to join health insurance or are associated with speed,
they can contact through this channel, they
can do it every day, it
is available in the description and I have
brought tears for you, but
before starting today's video, I would like to
request all of you,
please subscribe to my channel
and press the bell icon so that
you get the latest updates regarding, so let's
start, in today's video
I will give you an
option to
subscribe from 5  Subscribe till 12
about this method you
can get and if we
talk about constipation then in the meantime the volume
maximum entries are sour and the same
transformations are Islamic maximum only
tasty decide back to bother there is no
limit on that room rent
you can take Sindhi private room of any depth
and in that Stockholm Princess Line
you will get only private single stage sewing
available let's know about it receive from non
stop Congress only in both of us
you will get both individual and front rotor type
plants available if we talk about policy
term then Bad Gopal Mishra has
handsfree application system is Kare
Star for friendship nuvvu yes's power
system will be available now we will talk about the
most special benefits of England restore benefits
so in the crusher plant your white
shirt is grade point of collection
for modern times and from this you
can in the past of any disease in the house
and from this for BSP from the person for example who
came to his house and immediately after that if  If
other members of his family also get infected, then his
mother and his treatment will
cost them 10 lakh rupees. So you can
subscribe to this unlimited benefit.
Raghava's plan is
extended till the subscribe button but in this plan
automatic
syphilis will be available only once and subscribe to it
so that you get it from the very first day itself
which you can redeem on cash basis and rabbit basis
and in Pran from Star Congress
you will get health checkup from ₹2000 to
₹5000 then every central it means
if you do not take the plan then you will get health
checkup facility.
In Priyanka notification you are covered. In Rishabh Kam
you get Jupiter session for 7 days and
post fashion 180 rock this is cover for four
Congress from its preparation
years and for post graduation these days
you get
road ambulance ₹2000 environment and subscribe to this
mark
and also cover the
person in this mail is  Treatment back
cover is there, IS treatment cover is there in pressure application,
now in Dasha Star for Friendship Red,
maximum up to 3rd is IIS treatment,
you are aware, so let's now talk
about organ donor cover, in Reaction
Praniyan Star Comprehensive Plan,
you have organ donor expenses covered, now Durdasha,
apart from these benefits,
you also get maternity cover, whose wedding period
comes, then you get Unborn Baby cover ranging from
Rs 1 lakh to 2 lakh, in
which you have vaccination expenses
covered from ₹5000 to ₹10 lakh, which
you get in the school principal itself, for
normal delivery you get an award of 15
thousand to 50 thousand, and
in the case of Caesarean, you have a cover of 20 thousand to one lakh, if we
talk about people, then in Pressure
Plan, you get this boost
benefit at 50%, which goes to a maximum of 100%, that is,
your NAC is doubled at this time,
if in the policy term your
Double faced people are dear, what kind of button plate will it
reduce by fifty percent and in Stockholm
Principal you get
50% option a shot at every life and
maximum up to hundred percent with the button
it will reduce by 50% now let's talk about and
clear cash deposit, this is what you get
dish now I have given you ₹4000 in big star
comprehensive plan you get ₹500 to ₹
2500 per click
you get turmeric season benefit only in Mexico campus
if you take care of your health
and live turmeric then we give you our
thirty percent discount on
pimples and staff enhancement you have vellar
discount available now let's talk
about the comment PCs cut about the
previous treatment and see good treatment
second medical PM cataract surgery like
features then there is Islamic cover then cremation now let's
talk about student cover only you
get Mitthu Parmeshwar Lal Mirch two
five times and The Mission maximum up to 12
principal has accidental death and foreign
total duty  At the time of alcohol and
business, which you do
not get subscribed from then till
now, let us
know some features in the month to avail,
you get the facility of settlement of any third party,
health handsfree plane, send me,
apart from these you can take it in the network hospital of the company
and you can get tax benefit on payment of premium, that is, we
reduce the amount
which we have taken and
whose age is about 40 years,
then I
reduce it by 10,000 350 4955 example, so for example a
person's age is up to 40 years,
then Max Bupa Aishwarya
Tasla's Pradhan has 29 thousand 285 person
subscribed, 43 thousand 706 Shweta has
reduced it, so in the example we have taken and
now we have about
10 lakh 36 thousand 800
subscribed
295 and if you have
not subscribed then
please
click on the like button,
subscribe
2361 now as I told you
in the beginning of the video, so let's
Now let's talk about those people,
if you select this bank then it does
not hate you for all the items
like
subscribing to the company, now the second option which you will get is
50,000
subscriptions, consumer price index
subscription, whether you
save Congress and Pranayam,
after seeing this benefit, I found Ishwar plan to be the most
beneficial, you can contact us for more than 200 information
and details about four Congress, you can
take bribe with the help of the number, so
friends, this is all I hope in today's video,
we want to give you
an important information in this video, we
want to talk to all of you,
because of your continuous contribution,
how many people are connected to our channel for 14 years, you are with us
and if you subscribe to my channel
and our family,
then the speed will remain low till shameless, it is a
very good effort for you.